<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greenwood Project</title>
    <description>Introducing minority students to the financial industry</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 22:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 22:32:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greenwood Rings the Bell for Financial Literacy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Cboe Global Markets for inviting the Greenwood Project to Ring the Bell for Financial Literacy. #worldinvestorweek #financialliteracy #wiw2019 #financialempowerment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3UwTOV_p3BM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/greenwood-rings-the-bell-for-financial-literacy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/greenwood-rings-the-bell-for-financial-literacy/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Greenwood Impact</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Greenwood Project was founded in 2016 and has experienced rapid and tremendous success as we built out a program offering and proved that our model works. Throughout this journey, we knew it was critical to document all our success and most importantly the impact and outcomes of our work. This video helps to tell our story. Thank you to all our supporters, corporate partners and fans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/rhM5vbhuRY0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/the-greenwood-impact/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/the-greenwood-impact/</guid>
        
        <category>outcomes</category>
        
        <category>impact</category>
        
        
        <category>outcomes</category>
        
        <category>impact</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Life-Changing Summer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Alex Moreno and I am a rising freshman at the University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign. During high school, I was student-athlete playing soccer and baseball, a mentor, and a translator for international students. Additionally, I also participated in the National Hispanic Institute, a leadership program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/DSC_0197-37f001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;DSC_0197-37f001.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going into University, I was undeclared, but after participating in the Greenwood project this summer, and seeing all the opportunities available to me in financial services, I’ve realized that I want to major in economics. Coming from a low-income community, all I saw growing up were mechanics, carpenters, and gang members. A couple of my close friends did not make it all the way through high school and a major reason for that was the lack of professional individuals and mentors that we could look up to in our communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_9746.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_9746.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This summer I interned with the Greenwood Project to build my social capital and to network with individuals such as CEO’s, partners, recruiters at the many firms we visited. This summer with Greenwood I experienced what a day in the life of a financial professional was like, and saw first-hand how the markets affect a firms profitability. Being able to visit more than 20 companies in only six weeks was such an advantage because I got to explore different work environments and get an idea for which direction my career path may take me. I also learned about the many positions in the industry that I had no idea even existed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joining the Greenwood Project just after graduating high school has been the best choice I could have made for my future. I cannot thank Bevon Joseph and his wife Elois enough for starting this program to introduce minority students like myself to the financial industry, because without this opportunity I would not have this type of access. One big highlight for me this summer was meeting the Federal Reserve Bank Chairman, Charlie Evans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_9361.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_9361.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being the first in my family to participate in the Greenwood Project, allowed me to break a cycle in my family and gave me the opportunity to show my younger siblings that there is no limit to the things one can do. When there are great people such as Bevon and Elois willing to help, it is our duty to participate in order to get these types of positions in the industry for black and brown students. The Greenwood Project taught me that you although you might be very smart and doing well in school, without social capital it will be that much harder to break into the financial services industry. Thank you, Greenwood!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/alex-moreno/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/alex-moreno/</guid>
        
        <category>lunch and learn</category>
        
        <category>internships</category>
        
        <category>college</category>
        
        <category>Federal Reserve Bank</category>
        
        
        <category>University of Illionis Urbana Champaign</category>
        
        <category>Greenwood Project Financial Institute</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What I Learned From The Greenwood Project</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Kwintyn Essex and I am a rising senior at Eisenhower High School. I am a Link Unlimited Scholar and an Assistant Instructor at a Martial Arts School. This summer, I participated in the Greenwood Project’s FinTech  Cohort. I wanted to get a basic understanding of coding in case I wanted to further my knowledge for a career choice later in life, and I believed a summer interning for an organization that thrived in introducing students into the finance and technology world would be the best way to do that. I have always been interested in science and technology, and this program helped me realized that I could explore my interest even though I am in high school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_0185.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_0185.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Summer at the Greenwood Project, I was introduced to the coding language of Python. I learned basic coding terminology and learned how to create a program to track my spending. Besides learning to code, the Greenwood Project took me to many different companies to learn about finance careers. I was able to network and learn about the finance world which is something I would have never been exposed to if not for the Greenwood Project. I learned a lot at the Greenwood Project, but one of the most important things I learned that I can always take with me is my elevator pitch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_9741.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_9741.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, Greenwood has been an enlightening experience that I will always remember. Greenwood has opened doors for me, but it is my job to step through them. Greenwood has given me a new perspective on the finance world and is an all-around great program. I hope to further my knowledge of coding and continue to explore the many ways I could use this knowledge of programming in the finance world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 01:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/what-i-learned-from-the-greenwood-project/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/what-i-learned-from-the-greenwood-project/</guid>
        
        <category>internship</category>
        
        <category>Eisenhower High School</category>
        
        <category>Link Unlimited Scholar</category>
        
        <category>lunch and learn</category>
        
        
        <category>High School Fintech</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking Advantage of Every Opportunity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Emmanuella Nwokenkwo and I am a recent graduate of Thornwood High School. While at Thornwood, I was a student-athlete for 3 years playing volleyball, National Honors Society member, and Vice president of Student Council. I will be attending the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign in the fall majoring in Business Finance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/DSC_0084.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;DSC_0084.JPG&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This summer, I joined the Greenwood Project Financial Institute to learn more about the financial industry and build my social capital by networking with different people from various companies we visited. This summer I was able to visit 20 plus companies that range from investment banking to FinTech companies. I learned so much about the different careers within the financial industry, and I went from having 0 connections on LinkedIn to 105 connections in just six weeks. Going into the program I was only aware of careers such as a financial advisor, but the Greenwood Project exposed me to asset management, private wealth management, portfolio management, and many other careers that have given me more options and fields to explore in the future. Learning about the different work styles of each career has given me an insight into what I want to do in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/EMMA-8806ef.png&quot; alt=&quot;EMMA-8806ef.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the program, the high school cohort was split into two groups to pitch a stock to potential investors. I have been learning a lot about what to look for when picking a stock, keeping up with current news, and understanding the stock market lingo. As a result of my involvement in the Greenwood Project, I am currently investing in 3 stocks. I had no knowledge of investing prior to coming into the program and now I have my own brokerage account, this again proves how effective the Greenwood Program is. 
Besides the amazing knowledge I gained from the Greenwood Project about investing, I also grew my relationship with employees from two companies (Goldman Sachs and IDEX Corporation) we visited for a Lunch and Learn event for potential internship opportunities in the future. These are companies that I never thought I would be given the opportunity to work for prior to the Greenwood Project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being part of the Greenwood Project has opened my eyes to unlimited opportunities and has given me hope that someone like me can break into and strive in this industry. The opportunities Greenwood has exposed me to are unmatched and still feels unreal. I cannot thank Bevon and Elois enough for this amazing opportunity to be apart of the Greenwood Project. Greenwood has opened many doors and now it’s up to me to take advantage of those opportunities. For each lunch and learn event we had to prepare complex questions which not only challenged my knowledge but prepared me to understand the functions of each company. Overall, Greenwood has exposed me to many opportunities in the financial industry and I hope one day I can give back and make an impact on someone’s life the way Greenwood made on mine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/taking-advantage-of-every-opportunity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/taking-advantage-of-every-opportunity/</guid>
        
        <category>High School Financial Institute</category>
        
        <category>Thornwood High School</category>
        
        <category>University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign</category>
        
        
        <category>Internship</category>
        
        <category>Business Finance</category>
        
        <category>Greenwood Project Financial Institute</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Unforgettable Summer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Joshua Thornton, and I am a rising senior at De La Salle Institute. While at De La Salle, I am the Captain of our Men’s Varsity Basketball Team, an avid member of the Investment Club, Treasurer of the French Club and a National Honors Society Member. When I attend college, I plan on majoring in Business Finance and minoring in Accounting. This past summer, the Greenwood Project has helped me get connections in both fields.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Josh-1ad52d.png&quot; alt=&quot;Josh-1ad52d.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This summer at Greenwood Project I was in the high school Financial Institue Cohort. During the week, we attended Lunch and Learn events visiting different financial companies such as Goldman Sachs, Guggenheim Partners, Panduit, and William Blair. We also competed in a stock pitch competition. In the stock pitch competition, the two high school cohort groups were separated into teams to research one stock to pitch to investors (shark tank style). My group chose Alibaba, and we placed 1st in the competition, we learned how to perform proper market and stock research. The Greenwood Project taught us a lot about the markets and why it is important to invest in what you own and use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_9911.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_9911.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the Greenwood project has made a huge impact on me. My dad worked in the financial services industry for over 20 years as a Portfolio Manager for BMO Harris Bank, so coming into Greenwood I was already somewhat familiar with the inner workings of the financial industry. Nevertheless, the connections I was able to make because of the Greenwood project are second to none. I started with 0 connections on LinkedIn and am now approaching 90; all gained in 6 weeks. The friends I made while in the program, and the experiences I shared with them is something I truly will never forget. Greenwood is a great project with an even greater mission, and it certainly has lived up to its reputation for me. I can only thank them for all the opportunities they have given me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 03:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/an-unforgettable-summer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/an-unforgettable-summer/</guid>
        
        <category>internships</category>
        
        <category>High School Cohort</category>
        
        <category>De La Salle Institute</category>
        
        
        <category>2019</category>
        
        <category>High School Financial Institute</category>
        
        <category>Greenwood Project Financial Institute</category>
        
        <category>Senior in high school</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Sky is The Limit</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Joi Mays and I am a rising senior at Kenwood Academy High School. I am the President of our Humanitarian Society, Cultural Appreciation club, and I am a varsity competitor for Kenwood’s multi-award winning debate team. Through the Greenwood Project, I have gained more knowledge of American and overseas stock markets, and I can confidently say that the Greenwood Project has given me exposure to the financial industry which I otherwise would not have. Greenwood has helped me realize that there are endless career options for me in financial services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_9638.HEIC-79a3cf.png&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_9638.HEIC-79a3cf.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was part of the Greenwood Project Financial Institute Cohort, which meant that we visited a company a day for six weeks. We went from Wall Street powerhouses like Goldman Sachs to large international manufacturing companies like Panduit, to powerful technology-based companies like Braintree. At each company, we networked with the employees, interns, and even some of the senior leaders. It was amazing to see how many companies have diversity initiatives specifically geared towards students like myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Greenwood project has taught me that there is a career for me in financial services, and with hard work and dedication to my goals, the only limits for me are the ones I put on myself.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 02:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/the-sky-is-the-limit/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/the-sky-is-the-limit/</guid>
        
        <category>internships</category>
        
        <category>Kenwood Academy High School</category>
        
        <category>High School Cohort</category>
        
        
        <category>2019</category>
        
        <category>Senior in high school</category>
        
        <category>Greenwood Project Financial Institute</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Learning Experience in FinTech</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Niya Yates and I am a senior at Whitney Young Magnet High School. I have been studying Japanese at Whitney for three years and I plan to continue studying it throughout college. I won second place at the Japan Bowl, a state-wide Japanese academic competition for the State of Illinois. Using my computer science skills, I have also developed a website as well as a video game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_9531.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_9531.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This summer, I joined the Greenwood Project’s 6-week Fintech Coding Boot Camp. During this program, I learned to code in Python with the programming software called Jupyter Notebook. Also, Greenwood gave me guidance on how to write a resume, create an elevator pitch, and how to present myself in a corporate setting. I got to put these soft skills to use when I went on companies Lunch and Learn events with Greenwood. During the Lunch and Learn events, we visited companies such as Braintree, IDEX, and Chicago Trading Company, and I had the opportunity to network with the employees of these companies. As a result of the Greenwood Project, I learned a lot about job titles I didn’t even know existed, and I received lots of guidance for my future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/72241147-E360-4A56-92D7-D8D06F4BA524.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;72241147-E360-4A56-92D7-D8D06F4BA524.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greenwood has had a strong impact on my life because, without the Greenwood Project, I would not have the exposure to the corporate world I have today. Through the Greenwood Project, I was able to be exposed to the financial technology industry, which was completely new to me, and connect with people I would never have been able to network with outside of this program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had taken a computer science class before, but during these six weeks, I learned a lot about programming as well as many other things that my classes didn’t touch on. Overall, I am really grateful that I got this opportunity to learn things about the financial industry that aren’t taught in high school. Being a part of this program helped me realize to first, be grateful for the opportunities that present themselves to me, and second, when opportunities present themselves to me, run with it and don’t stop until I reach the finish line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 01:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/my-learning-experience-in-fintech/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/my-learning-experience-in-fintech/</guid>
        
        <category>internships</category>
        
        <category>Whitney Young High School</category>
        
        <category>Fintech</category>
        
        <category>High School Cohort</category>
        
        
        <category>2019</category>
        
        <category>Fintech</category>
        
        <category>High School Fintech</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dreams Into Reality</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Jonathan Hernandez and I am a rising junior at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign majoring in Agriculture and Consumer Economics with a Concentration in Financial Planning. Before I was introduced to the Greenwood Project, I did not know what I wanted to do with my major and how to turn my interest in the finance industry into a career. Coming from a background where my family and friends are not in the finance industry, it made it very difficult to learn about the finance industry and even more difficult to land an internship. After hearing about the Greenwood Project from a friend at my University, I eagerly reached out to Bevon, the co-founder of the organization, to learn more about the Greenwood Project. When I was accepted into the program, I made it a priority to put my best foot forward in everything I did. All I can say is that it was the best step I have ever made in my life. Thanks to the Greenwood Project, I have learned more about the financial industry with an expanded knowledge of financial literacy that has opened doors for my career path in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_9120.png&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_9120.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the Greenwood Project, I am interning at Oak Street Real Estate Capital, one of the largest private equity real estate firms, where I am creating financial models, offering memorandums, and learning how to develop client business relationships. Not only did Greenwood provide me with an amazing internship and guidance, but they also choose me, along with 12 other scholars, to fly out to New York City and experience the life of an employee on both the buy and sell-side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Jonny%20and%20Southwest-32c96c.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jonny and Southwest-32c96c.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, the Greenwood Project has been a great experience in regards to the finance industry, but most importantly, they provided me a support system for my education, for my career and as a long-term mentor.  Knowing that I have a group of like-minded and supportive peers and mentors, has given me the ultimate confidence that my dreams can become a reality.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/dreams-into-reality/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/dreams-into-reality/</guid>
        
        <category>University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign</category>
        
        <category>Oak Street Real Estate Capital</category>
        
        <category>college</category>
        
        <category>Wall Street</category>
        
        <category>internship</category>
        
        <category>Agribusiness</category>
        
        
        <category>entry level</category>
        
        <category>finance</category>
        
        <category>2019</category>
        
        <category>2019 Wall Street</category>
        
        <category>diversity</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Future Is My Canvas</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Arsema Tesfai and I am a rising sophomore at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign majoring in Political Science and minoring in Business. In the fall, I will serve as fundraiser chair for a mentoring organization on campus. I am interested in learning more about stocks, bonds, trades, and investing; as well as the allocation of money to different institutions like Chicago Public Schools. Through the Greenwood Project, I am interning at Chicago Board Options Exchange with Business First AM and Angela Miles. There I work on sales, production, marketing, and business news stories. Last week at Business First AM, I worked on booking a guest to speak on a news segment called Politics and Money as the subject matter corresponds with my major. I also tracked social media progress using an organized spreadsheet. Because Business First AM is relatively new to Instagram, I have been able to work on giving the page a fresh start with new ideas while watching the followers grow organically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Aresema%20Tesfai-187d5d.png&quot; alt=&quot;Aresema Tesfai-187d5d.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because this news station is spreading quickly, I helped Ms. Miles reach out to news station to ensure that all TV stations we are airing, are accounted for. In addition to advertising and marketing, I also worked on B-roll to insert into the news segments. B-roll involves researching different news stories affecting the stock market and inserting company clips or pictures to go along with it. The goal of Business First AM is to bridge the gap between Main Street and Wall Street. I feel as if my internship at Cboe and my time with the Greenwood Project has begun building the blocks to close that gap. Not only has my network grown, but my understanding of the American economy and the professional skills necessary to succeed in it have developed. Moving forward, my goals are to utilize the resources and connections that I have collected this summer to ensure that the lessons and experiences I have been provided do not get left behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/3CC31454-52F3-4218-8C85-F894C6A7BC11-7e424a.png&quot; alt=&quot;3CC31454-52F3-4218-8C85-F894C6A7BC11-7e424a.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every note, business card, or handshake is valuable to my future in the professional world. Along with utilizing all of my tools, I hope to pass along some of the tokens I’ve received from The Greenwood Project to future scholars. Before I attended Greenwood Project annual Wall Street, this summer has already been one of the most transformative summers. After the New York trip, my aspirations and goals became a reality. I know now that it does not always matter where you come from but where you are going. The Greenwood Project has opened up a lot of doors for me, and I plan to walk through every single one.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/arsema-tesfai/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/arsema-tesfai/</guid>
        
        <category>internships</category>
        
        <category>University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign</category>
        
        <category>Cboe</category>
        
        <category>College Cohort</category>
        
        
        <category>entry level</category>
        
        <category>2019</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
