<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greenwood Project</title>
    <description>Introducing Black and Latinx Students To The Financial Industry</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 19:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 19:29:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not Your Typical Summer Program</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Yomileigh Abdi, but everyone calls me Yomi. I am a rising senior at Northside College Prep where I am the Editor-in-Chief of the school newspaper and a member of two student organizations: Mu Alpha Theta and Economics and Investment Club. This summer, I am continuing my political science research internship and taking a finance class at Northwestern University as well as interning at the Greenwood Project Financial Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Yomi_headshot.png&quot; alt=&quot;Yomi_headshot.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I first heard about Greenwood through my AP Microeconomics teacher who posted the link on our Google Classroom page, and I was excited about the opportunity to explore the financial industry with like-minded individuals who looked like me. I wanted to learn about career paths in the financial sector and broaden my professional circle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the Greenwood Project, I was invited to work on two very exciting projects. The first is collaborating with a team of 5 college students to create a combined marketing plan for 8 small black-owned businesses in Bronzeville through the Quad Communities Development Corporation (QCDC) with the assistance of Marcus Lemonis. The second is working on a feasibility study for William Blair to vet and develop a concept paper on how to build a pipeline of minority high school students for financial services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/image.png&quot; alt=&quot;image.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m incredibly grateful for my experience at the Greenwood Project as it has been a truly worthwhile summer. The exposure has made me much more knowledgeable about the stock market, investing and other financial concepts that initially seemed esoteric. Every morning, I’ve started reading an Investopedia newsletter that summarizes the key headlines and insights of the global markets. It’s a small step but it allows me to slowly build my understanding with daily doses of current financial information in my inbox. I’m interested in attending an undergraduate business school and majoring in economics with a concentration in finance. My time at Greenwood has made me much more confident about my ability to succeed as a business major and a black woman in the financial industry.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/yomi/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/yomi/</guid>
        
        <category>Northside College Prep</category>
        
        <category>William Blair</category>
        
        <category>QCDC</category>
        
        
        <category>High School Financial Institute</category>
        
        <category>Greenwood News</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coming Prepared Is The First Step To Success</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Kevin Perkins and I am a rising Senior at Bradley University completing a Bachelor of Science degree in Social Media Marketing with a minor in Management and Leadership. At Bradley, I am involved in numerous leadership positions including treasurer and a peer mentor where I am able to assist minorities, promote marketing strategy and business and marketing development. The summer of 2020, I had the amazing opportunity to intern with The Greenwood Project and from them, I was not only offered an internship but a chance to work with eight small businesses on the South Side of Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Kevin_headshot-3764a6.png&quot; alt=&quot;Kevin_headshot-3764a6.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Greenwood Project is my first experience having an internship. I was introduced to the organization through a current scholar and I could say, this was one of the best decisions I have made. Having a marketing background, I had very little knowledge about finance, but knew that the only way I could gain experience is through experience. Throughout the summer, I participated in many workshops that covered topics that included banking and investing, basic understanding of trading,research analysis on IPOs, training on the Bloomberg Terminal, and professional etiquette. I was able to build relationships and discuss career paths with employers from some of the largest financial institutions including William Blair, Nasdaq, Option Pit, UBS, and many more. I’ve worked on bi-weekly projects presented by these firms that have exposed me to hands-on experience of what it’s like to work in different financial sectors. In addition, I accomplished a huge achievement by successfully completing courses to receive the Bloomberg Market Concepts certification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I am preparing to transition into my career, much like other students, I am seeking to continue strengthening my skills in the financial sector as well as gain more experience in various professions. All things considered, the Greenwood Project has presented me with a myriad of opportunities. In my experience, the Greenwood Project has improved my professional etiquette, expanded my network significantly, and matured my knowledge of the financial industry. Even though the journey isn’t finished, Bevon and the Greenwood Project have undoubtedly pushed me to work harder to achieve my goals. They motivated me even more to pursue my aspirations and continue to excel beyond expectations. Recently, I have accepted an offer to intern with TheStreet, a financial news and financial literacy website, with the help of Zev Fima and Bevon Joseph.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No matter what background students come from, the Greenwood Project is willing to open doors and create opportunities that are unmatched for anyone. I have learned that as long as you come prepared and ready to work, Greenwood will do everything they can to put you in a position to succeed. It has been life changing and I am truly grateful.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/coming-prepared-is-the-first-step-to-success/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/coming-prepared-is-the-first-step-to-success/</guid>
        
        <category>Bradley University</category>
        
        <category>College Cohort</category>
        
        <category>TheStreet</category>
        
        
        <category>social media</category>
        
        <category>Management and Leadership</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great Opportunities Are Unforgettable</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Elijah Crump and I am a Junior at Knox College where I Major in Integrative Business and Management. I am a 2020 Greenwood Scholar, and this summer proved to be one of the most unforgettable ever. I learned about the Greenwood Project during the summer of 2019 at a Knox College Black alumni event. At Knox, I am also on the men’s basketball team and a peer career leader in the career services office on campus. I am always interested in opportunities to expand my network and gain more exposure to the business world, so I was very excited to learn about the Greenwood Project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Elijah_Action.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Elijah_Action.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before finance, my primary focus was on marketing and gaining more experience in marketing using social media, the financial industry was not on my radar. Nevertheless, soon after beginning my first few weeks with Greenwood, I began trading real money with a foundational knowledge of how the market works. I began doing research, getting up earlier to watch international markets, and soon enough, I spoke the language of the Stock Market. As I was doing research I started to realize that this is something that I enjoyed and it made me rethink my career goals. Through Greenwood, I had the opportunity to obtain my Bloomberg Market Concepts Certification and CFA Foundations Certification.  One thing I have always wanted to do is give back to people who look like me and come from a similar background, and what better way than enhancing their financial literacy. I figured that I can take what I learned from finance and teach it to black and brown communities, because that’s something that we are not taught, it is something we typically have to seek out on our own. I want to be able to share my financial knowledge with kids from those communities so they are aware of the plethora of career pathways available to them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can say that joining the Greenwood Project was the best thing I could have done. Not only have I been enhancing my financial literacy and learning every day, but I have also been able to connect and talk with many industry leaders in Chicago and New York. Greenwood has given me the opportunity to connect with mentors in the financial industry who have become important resources for me. I worked on quite a few virtual projects this summer with Greenwood. Some of the companies I worked with included William Blair, Headwater Solutions, and the Chicago Trading company. This summer has forever altered my career trajectory. Thank you Greenwood Project!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/elijah-crump/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/elijah-crump/</guid>
        
        <category>Knox College</category>
        
        <category>Greenwood Project</category>
        
        <category>Integrative Business and Managment</category>
        
        
        <category>Greenwood News</category>
        
        <category>Bradley University</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Summer After Graduation during COVID-19</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Camron Durr, a recent graduate of the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign majoring in Finance with a minor in the Hoeft Technology and Management Program (a joint venture between the Gies college of business and the Grainger College of Engineering). Just prior to my last semester of college I was ecstatic to receive an email from the school congratulating me for graduating into one of the strongest US economies ever. Unfortunately, a few months later the coronavirus pandemic caused many of the firms I was interviewing with, to freeze their hiring indefinitely. Around the same time, I was thankful to be accepted into the Greenwood project and from the very start, Bevon Joseph, the President of Greenwood, personally assisted me in finding employment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Camron.png&quot; alt=&quot;Camron.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the Greenwood project, I have been able to network with so many inspiring industry mavericks who have helped me to focus my career goals but more importantly have enhanced my knowledge of the finance industry in general. During this summer Greenwood has ensured that I increase my marketability by completing certifications and micro internships with extraordinary firms including the Bloomberg Market Conceptions, CFA Foundations certification, and the SIE certification. Whether it be analyzing refinance risk for mortgage-backed securities, or synthesizing long positions in stock with options, or crafting an investment thesis, I have truly learned a lot and have been able to apply many concepts I learned in school to real life. Not to mention, I've had the opportunity to do a TV interview with NASDAQ and help small businesses in the Chicago better market themselves all in the midst of a global pandemic!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Camron2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Camron2.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the newfound skills and network, I have gained my prospects of becoming an investment banker are infinitely greater than they would have been otherwise. In fact, Greenwood has connected me with firms who are interested in interviewing me for their company. I am truly blessed to be apart of such a wonderful program and I am looking forward to helping others the way Greenwood has helped me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/my-summer-after-graduation-during-covid-19/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/my-summer-after-graduation-during-covid-19/</guid>
        
        <category>opportunities</category>
        
        <category>University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign</category>
        
        <category>College Cohort</category>
        
        
        <category>COVID-19</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Chance with The Greenwood Project</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Brian Miller Jr and I am a rising Senior at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign majoring in Agricultural Consumer Economics with a concentration in Finance and Agri-Business. I am a Greenwood Scholar and a Compliance Intern at the National Futures Association. Before I joined the Greenwood Project I was involved with a few clubs and organizations on campus but I felt that I needed to learn more about the financial industry to be prepared once I graduated. Due to COVID-19, my options were very limited to where I could intern.
&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Brian_headshot.png&quot; alt=&quot;Brian_headshot.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I kept looking for internships and resources and then one day a Greenwood Scholar and now alum, Lamar West, told me about the Greenwood Project and put me in contact with the CEO Bevon Joseph. Bevon knew little about me but accepted me as if he knew me his whole life. He provided me with resources to help build my resume, learn basic fundamentals about the stock market, and everything I needed to be successful in the financial industry. After a few conversations he saw that I was serious and dedicated and provided me with an internship opportunity I couldn’t refuse. That opportunity was an internship with the National Futures Association. I completed the interview and was selected to be an intern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My internship with the National Futures Association has taught me how to properly analyze bank statements,complete cash modules, and has given me hands-on experience with firms from the United Kingdom to Canada. If it wasn’t for the Greenwood Project I wouldn’t have gained this experience nor have such a wonderful internship. In addition to that the Greenwood Project provided me with the opportunity to complete the Bloomberg Market Concepts course. The course has enhanced my knowledge with stocks and trading and I now own various stocks and I’m currently reading books to self educate. Overall, the Greenwood Project has worked wonders for me and I believe organizations like this are needed to help students that were never given a chance in the financial industry.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/my-chance-with-the-greenwood-project/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/my-chance-with-the-greenwood-project/</guid>
        
        <category>Greenwood News</category>
        
        <category>NFA</category>
        
        <category>National Futures Assoication</category>
        
        <category>University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign</category>
        
        
        <category>entry level</category>
        
        <category>Internship</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Double The Opportunities</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Fatima Gutierrez and I am a rising Junior at Bradley University double majoring in Management and Leadership and Management Information System-Business Analytics with a minor in Spanish.
&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/FatimaHeadshotSP2020%5B1%5D.png&quot; alt=&quot;FatimaHeadshotSP2020[1].png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I first heard about the Greenwood Project during my freshman year at Bradley. I was reading the flyer posted on the wall while waiting for the elevators and I saw two words “Minority” and “Internships.” That was the moment I knew I had to look into this company.  Later in spring, I was able to meet Bevon Joseph, the Co-founder and President of Greenwood, at our spring career fair where I learned more about the Greenwood Project’s values and mission. Although I did not apply that summer, I always kept them in mind and later applied my sophomore year for Summer 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Greenwood Project has been the best thing that has ever happened to me this summer. I have learned so much about networking, options trading, portfolio management, mortgage rates, stock investing, and the list goes on and on. Thanks to the Greenwood Project I have also been able to obtain my Bloomberg Market Concepts (BMC) Certification, study for my CFA Investment Foundation Certification, and learn how to use the Bloomberg Terminal.
&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/Fatima_Action.png&quot; alt=&quot;Fatima_Action.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Greenwood Project also gave me the opportunity to obtain an internship at Northwestern Mutual-Chicago as an operations intern. I have had a great time learning about the company culture and meeting new people- an experience that has been amazing even through Zoom calls. I have enjoyed working on various projects and witnessing everything it takes for a company to operate effectively. I have been able to work closely and receive mentorship from Tara O’Dea who has been there to challenge me and guide me every step of the way. I was also given the amazing opportunity to interview with Jill Malandrino on Nasdaq TradeTalks show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A global pandemic did not stop the Greenwood Project from having summer internships and giving an opportunity for students to grow. They turned everything virtual and went above and beyond so the 2020 college cohort could gain as much experience in the finance industry as possible. I will be forever thankful to the Greenwood Project and Bevon Joseph because they saw something in me that I could not see in myself. I now know that I belong in these spaces and will continue to be successful in them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/double-the-opportunities/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/double-the-opportunities/</guid>
        
        <category>internships</category>
        
        <category>opportunities</category>
        
        <category>Spanish</category>
        
        <category>Greenwood News</category>
        
        <category>Greenwood Project</category>
        
        
        <category>Bradley University</category>
        
        <category>Fatima Gutierrez</category>
        
        <category>Management and Leadership</category>
        
        <category>Mangement Information System-Business Analytics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greenwood Project Continues Mission During COVID-19</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Greenwood Project is committed to introducing minority youth to the financial industry. In a typical summer, Greenwood Project scholars would take classes, visit firms, start internships, and host other programming. To adapt to COVID-19, we started working in early March to bring all of our programming online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are happy to announce that we are still offering all of our programming, simply modified to be virtual. The Greenwood Project team is setting up virtual, paid internships: Small teams will work virtually on projects assigned to them by our partner firms. In lieu of live networking events at firms, the Greenwood Project team has set up weekly Virtual Career Chats with industry professionals from a wide-variety of financial institutions. We have also developed a series of online courses (called the Greenwood Online Academy for Learning) for students to complete at their own pace ranging from topics like Interview Preparation to Programming in Python.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have also expanded on our typical offerings in hopes of providing even more support to students during this difficult time. We developed, in partnership with William Blair, a program to underwrite students’ costs to prepare and test for financial industry certifications. We also made our online classes available to any student, resulting in over 100 participants in our classes. We hope that this will expose even more students to our mission, encourage more minority students to consider the finance field, and create greater interest in applying for our summer institutes and internship programs in the future.&lt;br /&gt;
Simply, we are here for our students during COVID-19. They may need us, now, more than ever. The landscape of internships and hiring is more challenging now than we ever imagined. But, we are working hard to provide continued opportunities to give Greenwood Project scholars a leg up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We encourage all students to check out the Greenwood Online Academy for Learning and our Virtual Career Chats. For more information, email Charles at charles.turner@greenwoodproject.org. We also update our social media regularly with opportunities for anyone to become involved: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/greenwoodprochi/&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/greenwoodprochi/?hl=en&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/greenwoodprochi?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/company/greenwood-project/&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/greenwood-project-continues-mission-during-covid-19/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/greenwood-project-continues-mission-during-covid-19/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greenwood Rings the Bell for Financial Literacy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Cboe Global Markets for inviting the Greenwood Project to Ring the Bell for Financial Literacy. #worldinvestorweek #financialliteracy #wiw2019 #financialempowerment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3UwTOV_p3BM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/greenwood-rings-the-bell-for-financial-literacy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/greenwood-rings-the-bell-for-financial-literacy/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Greenwood Impact</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Greenwood Project was founded in 2016 and has experienced rapid and tremendous success as we built out a program offering and proved that our model works. Throughout this journey, we knew it was critical to document all our success and most importantly the impact and outcomes of our work. This video helps to tell our story. Thank you to all our supporters, corporate partners and fans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/rhM5vbhuRY0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/the-greenwood-impact/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/the-greenwood-impact/</guid>
        
        <category>outcomes</category>
        
        <category>impact</category>
        
        
        <category>outcomes</category>
        
        <category>impact</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Life-Changing Summer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Alex Moreno and I am a rising freshman at the University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign. During high school, I was student-athlete playing soccer and baseball, a mentor, and a translator for international students. Additionally, I also participated in the National Hispanic Institute, a leadership program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/DSC_0197-37f001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;DSC_0197-37f001.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going into University, I was undeclared, but after participating in the Greenwood project this summer, and seeing all the opportunities available to me in financial services, I've realized that I want to major in economics. Coming from a low-income community, all I saw growing up were mechanics, carpenters, and gang members. A couple of my close friends did not make it all the way through high school and a major reason for that was the lack of professional individuals and mentors that we could look up to in our communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_9746.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_9746.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This summer I interned with the Greenwood Project to build my social capital and to network with individuals such as CEO’s, partners, recruiters at the many firms we visited. This summer with Greenwood I experienced what a day in the life of a financial professional was like, and saw first-hand how the markets affect a firms profitability. Being able to visit more than 20 companies in only six weeks was such an advantage because I got to explore different work environments and get an idea for which direction my career path may take me. I also learned about the many positions in the industry that I had no idea even existed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joining the Greenwood Project just after graduating high school has been the best choice I could have made for my future. I cannot thank Bevon Joseph and his wife Elois enough for starting this program to introduce minority students like myself to the financial industry, because without this opportunity I would not have this type of access. One big highlight for me this summer was meeting the Federal Reserve Bank Chairman, Charlie Evans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/IMG_9361.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_9361.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being the first in my family to participate in the Greenwood Project, allowed me to break a cycle in my family and gave me the opportunity to show my younger siblings that there is no limit to the things one can do. When there are great people such as Bevon and Elois willing to help, it is our duty to participate in order to get these types of positions in the industry for black and brown students. The Greenwood Project taught me that you although you might be very smart and doing well in school, without social capital it will be that much harder to break into the financial services industry. Thank you, Greenwood!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/alex-moreno/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/alex-moreno/</guid>
        
        <category>lunch and learn</category>
        
        <category>internships</category>
        
        <category>college</category>
        
        <category>Federal Reserve Bank</category>
        
        
        <category>University of Illionis Urbana Champaign</category>
        
        <category>Greenwood Project Financial Institute</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
